http://www.fresno.edu/privacy-policy

Latest Coronavirus COVID-19 information available here
Close
Search
Search Programs & MajorsUndergraduateGraduateDegree CompletionBiblical SeminaryOnline ProgramsContinuing EducationSummer SchoolFacultyFPU WildernessNursingSTEMSocial Work ProgramStudy AbroadAdmissionUndergraduateTransferDegree CompletionBiblical SeminaryGraduateOnline ProgramsInternational StudentsVeteran ServicesCampus LifeHousing and Commuter LifeSpiritual Formation & DiversityStudent InvolvementStudent SupportCampus Life StaffAboutPresidentPresident's CabinetOur MissionStrategic PlanAccreditationFPU at a GlanceHistorySeminaryChurch RelationsConsumer InformationDiscrimination, Harassment, Sexual Misconduct and Title IX Sexual HarassmentDrug and Alcohol PolicyDisclosure DocumentsNewsEventsAthleticsArtsMusicTheaterVisual ArtsStudentsAcademic Success CenterALASBookstoreCareer DevelopmentDisability ServicesHiebert LibraryIT ServicesMy FPURegistrar's OfficeSeminary StudentsStudent Financial ServicesSunbirdCentralAlumniAlumni & Friends Tour of FranceAlumni AwardsAlumni ID CardsAlumni Mentor FormAlumni eNewsBenefits and ServicesCareer Development for AlumniFPU & AmazonSmileKeep Us UpdatedParentsCareer Development for ParentsServices and ResourcesStay ConnectedVisiting CampusStaff & FacultyCareer DevelopmentCenter for Online Learning (COL)Drug & Alcohol PolicyIntranetMy FPUSunbirdCentralVisitorsCampus SafetyCareersHuman ResourcesResources for EmployersSummer CampsCenter for Community TransformationCenter for PeacemakingGiveBenefits of GivingGiving OpportunitiesWays to GiveFPU FoundationAdvancement StaffDonor Honor RollLocationsBakersfield CampusFresno Main CampusMerced CampusNorth Fresno CampusVisalia CampusOnlineDirectoryA-Z 1-559-453-20001717 S. Chestnut Ave. Fresno, California 93702-4709 Apply nowVisit campusGive
HomePrivacy Policy Privacy Policy Information We Collect AutomaticallyIf you visit Fresno Pacific University websites to browse, read or download information:Your web browser automatically sends FPU (and we may retain) information such as:the internet domain through which you access the Internet (e.g., yourServiceProvider.com if you use a commercial Internet service provider, or yourSchool.edu if you use an Internet account from your school)the IP address of the computer you are usingthe browser and operating system you are usingthe date and time you access our sitethe URL of the site from which you linked directly to our siteWe will use this information as aggregate data to help us maintain this site, e.g., to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our site, to ensure the site is working properly and to help us make our site more accessible and useful.We will not use this information to identify individuals, except for site security or law enforcement purposes.We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information.Other Information We CollectIf you choose to identify yourself (or otherwise provide us with personal information) when you use our online forms:We will collect (and may retain) any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address and phone number, and any other information you provide. We will use this information to try to fulfill your request and may use it provide you with additional information at a later time. We will not disclose such information to third parties, except as specified in this privacy policy.If you request information, services or assistance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties that (in our judgment) are appropriate in order to fulfill your request. If, when you provide us with such information, you specify that you do not want us to disclose the information to third parties, we will honor your request. Note, however, that if you do not provide such information, it may be impossible for us to refer, respond to or fulfill your request.If your communication relates to a law enforcement matter, we may disclose the information to law enforcement agencies that we deem appropriate. How Long We Keep InformationWe reserve the right to retain all information provided indefinitely.SecurityPlease note that electronic communication, particularly email, is not necessarily secure against interception. Please do not send sensitive data (e.g., Social Security, bank account or credit card numbers) by email or web form unless necessary.  When submitting credit card numbers for ecommerce, please note that the university adheres to current PCI-DSS standards for the treatment of credit card information.CookiesWe may use cookies to customize this site for return visitors. These cookies are not required for site functionality. Additionally, third-party widgets such as YouTube or Flickr may install cookies depending on their configuration. You are not required to accept any cookies to use this site.Google AnalyticsWe use a tool called Google Analytics to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.Brightedge (www.fresno.edu only)Brightedge Self-Connecting-Pages collects session information that is used by the Self-Connecting-Pages to calculate relevance between pages and optimize the internal link graph. Information collected through this request includes:Session IDPage SequenceCurrent Page URLUser AgentReferring URLNo personally identifiable information (PII) is used by Brightedge Self-Connecting-Pages. As per standard industry practices, IP addresses are collected in log files for security and debugging purposes only. IP address data is not used by any BrightEdge systems, including BrightEdge Self-Connecting-Pages. BrightEdge does not utilize IP addresses, nor combine (directly or indirectly) IP addresses with any other information, to identify any natural person.Links to Independent WebsitesWebsites hosted by Fresno Pacific University may link to independently run websites outside of the http://fresno.edu domain and subdomains. Fresno Pacific is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites.  Last updated: 7/15/20 to add Brightedge section
